http://www.runegrammofon.com/policies/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Rune Grammofon
Welcome to our new site!
Login /
Register
Search
Cart
(0)
Search
Search
Close
Welcome to our new site!
Privacy policy
Rune Grammofon AS Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from runegrammofon.com (the “Site”).PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECTWhen you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”We collect Device Information using the following technologies:- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.- “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.
COOKIES IN USE
Cookies Necessary for the Functioning of the Store:
Name
Function
_ab
Used in connection with access to admin.
_secure_session_id
Used in connection with navigation through a storefront.
Cart
Used in connection with shopping cart.
cart_sig
Used in connection with checkout.
cart_ts
Used in connection with checkout.
checkout_token
Used in connection with checkout.
Secret
Used in connection with checkout.
Secure_customer_sig
Used in connection with customer login.
storefront_digest
Used in connection with customer login.
_shopify_u
Used to facilitate updating customer account information.
Reporting and Analytics
Name
Function
_tracking_consent
Tracking preferences.
_landing_page
Track landing pages.
_orig_referrer
Track landing pages.
_s
Shopify analytics.
_shopify_fs
Shopify analytics.
_shopify_s
Shopify analytics.
_shopify_sa_p
Shopify analytics relating to marketing & referrals.
_shopify_sa_t
Shopify analytics relating to marketing & referrals.
_shopify_y
Shopify analytics.
_y
Shopify analytics.
tracked_start_checkout
Shopify analytics relating to checkout.
HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:Communicate with you;Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; andWhen in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.
We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.DO NOT TRACKPlease note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.YOUR RIGHTSIf you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.DATA RETENTIONWhen you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.CHANGESWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
CONTACT USFor more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at rune@grappa.no or by mail using the details provided below:Akersgata 7, 0158 Oslo, Norway
Inbox me!
Sign up to our newsletter and we’ll keep you up to date with the latest arrivals
© 2020 Rune Grammofon.
Powered by Shopify
Mastercard
Visa
